Previously on Desperate Housewives
《绝望的主妇》前情提要
Mike's plan to propose to Susan...
Mike打算向Susan求婚...
These things don't belong to Jane
- 这些东西不是Jane的
"Mike Delfino."...was a surprise to Ian.
- "Mike Delfino" 让Ian大吃一惊
Monique was murdered... there's been an accident.
Monique被谋杀... - 这是个意外
And Orson... don't forget your wrench.
而Orson... - 别忘了你的扳手
...passed the blame.
嫁祸他人
A connection was made.
一段关系建立
Ahem!
A heart was broken,
让一颗心受了伤
And Bree buried her husband Rex.
Bree埋葬了他的丈夫Rex
My name is Rex Van De Kamp.
我叫Rex Van De Kamp
I always hated cemeteries when I was alive.
我活着的时候总是很讨厌公墓
Now that I'm dead, I like 'em even less.
现在我死了 就更加讨厌了
Here's where I used to live--
这里是我曾经生活的地方
A whole lot nicer, don't you think?
更加漂亮了 你不觉得吗
The place hasn't changed much since I left--
从我离开后 这地方没怎么变过
As tasteful and tidy as ever.
精致整洁如一
Everything perfect...
一切都那么完美...
At least on the surface.
至少表面上是这样
My family was the same way.
我的家庭还是一样
Look at us. You'd never guess
瞧瞧我们 你永远想不到
How ticked off we all were the day this was taken,
过去的那些日子里 我们有多么"气焰"嚣张
But that was the thing about us Van De Kamps.
但我们Van De Kamp家就是这样
To really fit in,
要想融入其中
You had to have a smile that gave away nothing.
你要学会用微笑来掩盖一切
Like my son Andrew-- To look at him,
好比我的儿子Andrew 看着他
You'd never know he spent six months on the streets
你永远想不到他曾有6个月的时间 在街上流浪
Supporting himself
为了养活自己
With panhandling and light prostitution.
只能靠乞讨或出卖身体
Or my daughter Danielle--
又好比我女儿Danielle
Does she look like the kind of girl
她看起来像是那种
Who'd seduce her middle-aged history teacher?
勾引自己中年历史老师的女孩儿吗?
I mean, they're my kids, and I love 'em,
他们是我的孩子 我爱他们
But I'm pretty darn relieved to be dead.
但这一死 真是让我解脱了
Here's the clown Bree replaced me with--
这位就是Bree找来替代我的小丑
Orson.
Orson
I don't mind saying,
说实话
He's creeped me out right from the get-Go.
他从一开始就让我背后发凉
(Blows
To me, he always has the shifty look
在我看来 他脸上总有一种诡异的表情
Of a guy who knows where the bodies are buried...
一个知道尸体埋在哪里的男人所有的表情...
And he should know.
他也应该知道
He buried them.
是他埋了他们
But Bree thinks he's sir galahad.
但Bree却觉得他是个圣洁的人
The kids like him.
孩子们喜欢他
And all my friends...
还有我的朋友们...
Now his friends. So it pleases me to know
现在都成了他的 所以我很高兴知道
That at least one of my old neighbors
至少我的老邻居中有一个人
Sees right through the guy.
看透了这个男人
Mike, you, uh, you just missed Bree.
Mike 你..呃...你跟Bree错过了
She's off to see her folks,
她去看她的家人了
And then we're finally taking our honeymoon.
我们终于要去度蜜月了
Yeah, not a bad time for you to leave town, is it?
是啊 这时候离开这里刚好 不是吗?
Well, I don't follow you.
我不懂你的意思
I just keep thinking about that night at Monique's place--
我一直在想那晚在Monique那里
How you made sure I left with my wrench,
你怎么会肯定我留下了我的扳手
The one with her blood on it.
上面沾有她的血迹
Well, it was your wrench.
那就是你的扳手啊
Why are you rehashing this?
你干吗老是抓着这件事不放呢?
My ex-wife confessed in her suicide note.
我前妻自杀时 留的条子上已经承认了
The case is closed.
这个案子已经结束了
Maybe it shouldn't be.
或许不该这么早就结束
What do you think the police would say
If they knew you were there that night?
你觉得如果警察知道那晚你也在场 他们会怎么想呢?
What do you think they'd say
If they knew you threw me off a roof?
那你觉得如果他们知道你把我扔下楼顶 他们又会怎么想呢?
Oh, Mike.
噢 Mike
We could make so much trouble for each other,
我们要想给彼此找麻烦太容易了
Or we can forget what we think we know
And be good neighbors.
还是说我们就忘记所知道的一切 做好邻居呢?
Your call.
你决定
No, Orson Hodge isn't exactly the guy
不 Orson Hodge并不是
I'd have picked to head my family,
我所希望来为我家人护航的那个人
But I'll give him one thing--
但有一件事我得承认
He's got the smile down cold.
他的笑冰冷刺骨
《绝望的主妇》 第三季 第16集
Take a drive down any street in suburbia.
在郊区的任何一条路上开车
Know what you're gonna see?
知道你会看到什么吗?
Deerate women.
绝望的女人们
That's right--
没错
One unhappy housewife after another,
不幸福的家庭主妇 一个接一个
Each completely miserable...
每个都活在自己独有的方式里
In her own unique way.
感受着彻底的痛苦
But I don't want to talk about them.
但我不想谈论她们
No, I want to talk about their men
不想 我要说的是她们的男人
And what happens to a guy
对一个男人来说
When that special lady in his life starts to lose it.
当他们生命中那个特别的女人将不复存在 他们会变得怎样
Like my friend Carlos.
比如我的朋友Carlos
He used to have it all--
他曾拥有一切
How wife, tons of dough,
怀抱佳人 腰缠万贯
Then bam!
结果突然之间
She gets a divorce, and he gets stuck with the bill.
她要离婚 他得到的只有一大堆帐单
But does he sit around and complain
Like your average hausfrau?
但是他有坐在那里像大多的主妇那样 抱怨个没完吗?
No, sir.
他没有
He finds creative ways
他想了很多办法
To get what you can out of life.
来得到生活能给予的一切
Hey, bro! Where you off to? Oh, the hospital called.
- 嘿 兄弟! 你要去哪儿啊? - 噢 医院打电话来
They found the stuff I had on me the night of the accident.
他们找到了我出意外那晚的东西了
Wow. Coma, murder rap-- You've had a tough year, buddy.
喔 昏迷 涉嫌谋杀 你这一年可真够难过的啊 兄弟
You know what you need? Some pampering.
你知道你需要什么吗? 一些优待
tomorrow you're checking in to a nice hotel.
明天你去家豪华酒店开房
Room service, jacuzzi, my treat.
客房服务 泡泡浴 我请客
You trying to get me out of the house?
你想把我从这儿支走么?
Mike, why would I-- Okay, there's this girl.
Mike 我干吗要...好吧 因为有个女孩
I knew it.
我就知道
Dude, she's a dancer,
伙计 她是个跳舞的
And if her online profile's any indication,
如果她在网上的简介里有说明
She's a complete freak.
她是个怪人
We're talking serious daddy issues.
我们说的是很严重的恋父情节
Look, I'll stay in my room. You'll never hear me.
听我说 我就待在房间里 不会弄出声音的
Yeah but you'll hear me. I'm kind of exuberant by nature,
是啊 但我们会有声音的 我是天生就比较"热情洋溢"
And when I haven't had it in a while,
再加上有段时间没有
I kind of do this shrieking thing that,
做这种会尖叫的事
I mean, is kinda-- Okay. All right, I'll go. Just stop talking.
- 我是说 这个.... - 好吧 我走 别说了
Thanks, pal. I wouldn't want it
To put a weird spin on our friendship.
谢了 兄弟 我不想给我们之间的友情找别扭
Too late.
太晚了
This is my friend Tom.
这位是我的朋友Tom
Have you heard what he's been up to lately?
你有听说他最近在干什么吗?
Thsilly bastard opened up his own pizza place.
这个笨蛋竟然开了一家自己的匹萨店
He thought that if he was his own boss,
他觉得如果自己当了老板
He could sleep in as late as he wanted,
他可以想睡多久就睡多久
But the problem with that logic is that married guys...
但这个逻辑并不适用于已婚男子
Hey. It's after 9:00.
嘿 已经9点多了
Come on, Thomasina, it's time to get up.
快点 Thomasina 该起床了
Are never their own boss.
他们永远做不了主
Are you as tired as I am?
你跟我一样累吗?
More, but I'm tougher, and I complain less.
比你还累 但我更坚强 我不爱抱怨
Not when you give birth, and you do that a lot.
你生孩子那会儿可不是 这方面你可是长项
Yeah? Ow!
- 是吗? - 嗷!
Before I forget, you got a call from Chez Nous
趁我还没忘 ChezNous打来电话
Confirming your reservation for our anniversary.
确认我们周年纪念你的预约
You heard that? I wanted that to be a surprise.
你听到了? 我本想给你个惊喜的
Well, we've been going there for the last seven years.
得了吧 我们过去7年都去的那里
It's not exactly a surprise. Anyway, I hope you don't mind,
这根本不算是惊喜 不过我希望你不要介意
But I canceled.
我取消了
You canceled? Why?
取消了? 为什么啊?
Honestly, I just don't feel up to going out this year.
说实话 我今年不想出去
But it's our anniversary. It's our ninth anniversary.
可这是我们的纪念日啊 9周年纪念日
Come on. The "big nine."
拜托 这可是重要的9年啊
That's a year longer than my mom said we would be married.
这比你妈妈说我们会在一起的时间要长一年呢
Come on. We gotta party down.
别这样 我们可要狂热派对呢
I'm exhausted.
我太累了
Honestly, all I wanna do is pawn the kids off on somebody else,
说实话 我想要的就是把孩子送到别人那里
Take a long bath and be in bed by 8:00.
舒舒服服洗个澡 然后8点就上床睡觉
Okay.
好吧
Oh, thank you.
噢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank yo mwah.
谢谢谢谢
Hold it.
等下
What about my sex?
那做爱呢?
I always get sex on our anniversary.
每年的纪念日我可都是有爱可做的啊
We can still have sex. Just try not to wake me.
我们还是可以做爱啊 就是你别把我弄醒了
This is Ian.
这位是Ian
Don't really know the guy,
对他真的是不太了解
But Susan Mayer seems to like him.
但是Susan Mayer好似很喜欢他
The other night,
那一晚
He surprised her with a proposal.
他突然向她求婚
She said yes, but he's still a little skittish
她答应了 但他仍然觉得有点不放心
About the competition.
面对这样的对手
But Ian knows that if love is war...
但是Ian知道 如果这是场爱的战争...
Hey. Where were you off to so early this morning?
嘿 这么早你去哪儿了啊?
Sometimes you gotta bring out the big artillery.
有时你要拿出重量级的武器
I should have d it when I proposed.
我本该在求婚时拿着这个的
It's not very good form, I know.
我知道式样不是很好看
Ian, oh, you can't be serious.
Ian 噢 你不是认真的吧
Oh, oh, that's just... too much.
噢 噢 真是...太过了啊
It's huge. Well, we could go smaller.
这太大了 我们可以要小一点的
Oh, no. No one's saying smaller.
噢 不 谁说要小的了
No, that's crazy talk.
不要 真是疯了
Rock me.
给我戴上
Oh!
噢!
Oh, my! Oh, it's so beautiful!
噢 天哪! 噢 真是太美了!
Oh! Oh! Oh, okay. Ay, nobody move.
噢! 噢 噢 好了 别动
I got it.
我捡到了
I knew I should have measured your finger. No, it's okay.
- 我知道我该先量一下你的手指 - 没关系的
I can get it resized.
我拿去改一下尺寸
You should go to the jeweler's right now,
你该现在就去珠宝店
And when you get back,
等你回来的时候
We can go and look at some places for the reception. Reception?
- 我们可以去看看几个办宴会的地方 - 宴会?
Yes, I was hoping we could pull this together for next month.
是的 我希望我们可以下个月就办
What's the rush? Am I pregnant? Of course not.
- 干吗这么着急? 我怀孕了吗? - 当然不是
I just--Well, I just can't wait to be married to you.
我只是...我只是等不及要娶你了
Are you sure? 'Cause you seem a little anxious.
真的吗? 我怎么觉得你有点不安呢
What would I have to be anxious about?
我有什么好不安的呢
Again, sorry for the mix-up.
再次抱歉把东西搞混了
If you could just sign right here...
你可以在这里签个字吗?
I don't remember this. You sure that's mine?
我不记得这个了 你确定这个是我的?
It was on you the night you were admitted.
那晚在你身上找到的 你认可过的
I got hit by a car.
我被车撞了
I don't remember anything about that night.
那晚的事我全都忘了
Well, it looks like you were gonna propose to someone.
看来你像是要跟某人求婚
"Susan, be mine forever. Mike."
"Susan 永远和我在一起 Mike"
Does that ring a bell?
想起来什么了吗
Sure does.
当然
Hey, Carlos.
嘿 Carlos
Hi. I have a little visitor
嗨 我有个客人来
That I thought you might get a kick out of seeing.
或许你愿意见见
Remember my little boy?
记得我的小宝贝吗
Hey, Travers. How you doing? Put her there.
嘿 Travers 你好吗? 来击掌
I'm Carlos Solis.
我是Carlos Solis
I think you came by my house one time trick-or-treating.
我记得你来过我家要糖吃
I remember. You gave me a protein ba
我记得 你给了一根蛋白棒
Right.
没错
Sorry. My wife forgot to buy candy.
抱歉 我太太忘了买糖
(Whistle blows)
Hey, is that football I hear? Go on. Check it out.
嘿 是在看橄榄球比赛吗? 走 去看看
I didn't know your son was coming for a visit.
我不知道你儿子要过来拜访
Neither did I.
我也是
His, uh, father just dumped him here for four weeks
他...他爸爸这四个星期把他扔在我这儿了
So he could jet off with his doctors without borders buddies
这样他就可以跟他那帮医生们一起
And fix cleft palates in kenya.
到肯亚去治疗什么唇裂病
Selfish son of a bitch.
自私鬼
Oh, come on. I mean, you barely even see him.
噢 拜托 你都没怎么见过他
It'll be fun-- A chance to bond.
会很有意思的 连接纽带的时刻
Yeah, that's true, but, um...
是啊 没错 但是...
I have this major party tonight,
我今晚有个重要的派对
And I was wondering if maybe you could
我在想你是不是可以
Just keep an eye on him for a few hours.
帮我照看他几个小时
Sorry. I can't tonight. Oh! Come on! You love kids.
- 抱歉 今晚不行 - 噢 别这样 你喜欢小孩子的啊
I mean, didn't you rent that chinese chick
So that you could have one of your own?
我是说 你请那个中国小妞 不就是为了有你自己的孩子吗?
I have a date, too, with a chick so hot
我也有约会 跟一个很火辣的小妞
I had to turn off the smoke alarms in my house.
我得关掉家里的防火警报 (指那个女生很火辣 )
Fine. Travers, come on. Let's go.
好吧 Travers 我们走
This isn't a child-friendly house.
这里不欢迎小孩子
Bye, Travers.
再见 Travers
It's good to see you.
很高兴见到你
Wow, she's a looker.
喔 她真漂亮
I'll say.
的确
Hey, what time's that fund-raiser? You got an hour.
- 嘿 募捐是几点? - 你有一个小时
Well, then...
好的 那...
Let'have a little fun.
我们找点乐子吧
Look what you did!
瞧你干的好事!
Don't yell at me. I'm just a passenger.
别对我大喊大叫 我只是坐车的
Well, your driver's an idiot!
好 你的司机是个白痴
Hey, it's not Clyde's fault.
嘿 不是Clyde的错
I mean, what man wouldn't be distracted by such beauty?
我是说 面对这样的美丽事物 哪个男人会不分心呢?
Now you're hitting on me?
你是在跟我搭讪么
I was talking about the car.
我是在说车子
Well, good. I'm glad you like it,
好 很高兴你喜欢我的车
'Cause you're gonna pay to fix this.
因为你要掏钱给我修好
Of course. $5,000 cover it?
当然 5000够了吗?
Five?
5?
Well, sure, I guess.
我估计够了吧
I'd rather not file an insurance claim.
我想就不要牵扯到保险索赔了
My opponent could find out and try to make me look bad. Opponent?
- 我的竞争对手会借此诋毁我的 - 对手?
Oh, well, I guess you don't read the papers.
噢 看来你不看报纸的
I'm running for mayor. My name's Victor Lang,
我在竞选市长 我是Victor Lang
And I hope I can count on your vote.
希望可以得到你的支持
I think I'd rather vote for the other guy--
我想我还是投票给另一个吧
You know, the one who didn't wreck my car?
就是没把我车子撞坏的那个
Oh, you're off yougame.
噢 你失手了啊
You didn't even get a phone number.
你连电话号码都没搞到
Oh, don't worry. I'll be seeing her again.
噢 别担心 我会和她再见的
How can you be so sure?
你怎么这么肯定
I didn't sign the check.
支票上没签字
What the hell are you doing? We need to talk.
- 你这是干吗啊? - 我们得谈谈
No, we don't. Get out. Please. You won't return my calls.
- 不 不用了 下车 - 拜托 你都不回我电话
Well, I've been busy.
我太忙了
Plus, my mom caught you naked on top of my friend.
再说我妈看到你光着身子 压在我朋友身上
Just read this, and if you still don't want to talk to me,
看看这个 如果你还是不想跟我说话
Then I'll never bother you again.
我就再也不会烦你了
Fine, I'll read it,
好 我看
But only if you get out of the car right now.
除非你现在马上给我下车
Now? But the-- The hot wax is starting.
现在? 这正开始喷热蜡呢
I know. Ticktock.
我知道 赶紧的
Uh...
Aah!
You're still in there?
你还在里面吗
How long does it take to pluck that unibrow?
你还要多久才把你的连眉拔完啊?
Leave me alone! Danielle, I have to be at work in ten minutes.
- 少理我! - Danielle 我还有10分钟就要去上班了
Now can I please just come in and brush my teeth?
请你让我进去把牙刷了 行吗?
I'm having a really bad day, all right?
我今天难过死了 好吗
Just go away!
走开
I'm gonna have a really bad day, too.
我也好过不了了!
I tend not to get tipped when my breath stinks.
我要是口气熏天就拿不到小费了
I'm pregnant.
我怀孕了
Mike, what are you doing here?
Mike 你在这儿干吗?
Oh, hey, um, I'm just selling some old jewelry.
噢 嘿 呃..我来卖以前的珠宝
I spoke to my manager.
我跟经理谈了
There's gonna be a charge to remove the inscription,
要想改掉上面的字需要另付费的
But, uh, we can refund you for the engagement ring.
但我们可以帮你退了这枚订婚戒指
That'll be fine.
很好
Was that the ring that you bought for...
那枚戒指是你买来...
Yeah.
是的
Can I help you?
有什么需要帮忙的吗
Uh, yeah, I, uh, have to get this sized.
是的 我....我要把这个戒指的尺码改一下
It's--It's a little loose.
有点...太松了
Do you know your size? No.
- 你知道你的尺寸吗 - 不知道
Congratulations, by the way.
恭喜你了
Ian... seems great.
Ian...人很不错
Thanks.
谢谢
I can't find my sizer.
我找不到量尺寸的仪器了
Um, here.
来
Try this one.
试试这个
Oh, no, th--
噢 不行
How's that fit?
大小如何?
It's perfect.
刚刚好
Great.
好
Can I have it back now?
请问我现在能拿回来吗?
Oh! Oh, Sorry.
哦! 哦 对不起
Hey, you've got a cousin in the Limo business, don't you?
嗨 你有个表哥在Limo公司 是不是? (Limo豪华型大轿车)
Actually, I've got a cousin
事实上 我有个表哥
In the "Limo as a front for prostitution" business.
他是在"如Limo般享受的色情生意"
He's in jail. Why do you ask?
他在坐牢 你为什么问?
Oh, I'm, uh, I'm just planning a big thing for my anniversary.
哦 我 哦  我只是想为我的结婚纪念日订一些计划
Aren't you just gonna go to chez boring,
你们不去无聊的Chez了
Like you do every year?
像往年一样?
No. Lynette's so over that,
不 Lynette烦透了那样
She was ready to bag the whole night,
她准备睡一整晚
So got me thinking.
所以让我有了个好主意
Nine years-- Time to shake things up.
9年了-- 时间改变了很多东西
Now I'm planning the greatest anniversary of all time.
现在我计划着有史以来最好的纪念日
Check this out.
听着
Lynette's gonna open the door
Lynette一打开门
To find a Limo driver with a dozen roses and a card.
就可以看到一个Limo的司机 手持一束鲜花 还有一张卡片
The card is gonna tell her to go with the guy,
卡片上会写着让她跟着司机走
Not ask any questions.
什么也不要问
He'll drive her out to the country.
他会开车把她带到乡村
He'll drop her off,
然后叫她下车
Then drive away.
接着把车开走
Just as she is starting to freak out,
当她开始害怕的时候
I show up in a horse-drawn carriage,
我驾着马车出现了
Which takes us up to whitman's bluff,
然后我们去Whitman's Bluff
Where we eat a catered dinner,
在那我们共进晚餐
Listen to a professional violinist.
听着美妙的小提琴
Afterwards, when we come home,
之后 当我们回家
I'm sure Lynette will think of a way to thank me.
我保证Lynette会有一种特别的方式来谢我
You're one romantic son of a bitch.
你真他妈的浪漫到家了
Wh-Hoo! I have my moments.
呜-呼! 我的美好时光啊
Of course I'm not questioning mayor Johnson's family values.
当然我不是质疑Johnson市长的家庭观
I'm sure they're what prompted him
我确定他们想他尽快
To put his sisters, brother-in-law
让他姐妹 姐夫妹夫
And six of his cousins on the city payroll.
还有6个表兄妹有钱领
Now, uh, if you'll excuse me,
现在 哦 请先离开一会
I have to cut this interview short.
我们的谈话先停一下
I have some very important business to attend to.
我有非常重要的事情要谈一下
Ms. Solis,
Solis小姐
What a nice surprise.
真是太意外了
Are you here to make a contribution to my campaign?
你是不是来为我的参选帮忙?
Not exactly.
并不是
Oh, no. Did I forget to sign--
哦 不会吧 我忘了签--
I'm so sorry.
万分抱歉
Let me make it up to you.
让我补偿一下
I'll take you to dinner.
我们一起去晚餐好不好
My treat.
我请客
It would be your treat.
当然你请客
I'm a hot date.
想和我约会的人多得很
What's in it for me?
你有什么特别之处?
Well, I have, uh, "an ingratiating wit,
哦 我有 哦 "过人的智慧"
Trustworthy smile,"
"让人值得信赖的微笑"
According to the "plainview herald."
"Plainview Herald"上写的
Yeah. Check, please.
好 请签名
My family also owns Lang enterprises.
我的家庭拥有Lang氏企业
Dad's worth a...
我爸爸的财产有...
Few hundred mil.
几亿
Well, a girl's gotta eat.
那好吧 女生总是要吃东西的
Great. I'll take you to Cucina.
太好了 我带你去Cucina
There's no place harder to get into.
没有哪里比这家更难订位子了
That's what you think.
那是你这样认为
Mike, this is completely unnecessary.
Mike 这完全没有必要
My paying for your lawyer was a favor. It wasn't a loan.
我给你付律师费是帮忙 不是借给你
I-I appreciate it, but I just don't like to owe anybody.
我..我很感谢你 但我不想欠任何人
Well, I-I just don't want you
哦 我...我 我只是不想
To have any trouble getting back on your feet.
你有什么麻烦 尽快回到自己原有的生活
No, it's fine. I had a windfall. The hospital gave me back
没关系 我得了一点意外之财 医院还给我一枚订婚戒指
An engagement ring I didn't even know I had.
我都不记得这枚戒指的存在
Oh, really? So you sold it?
哦 是吗? 你把戒指卖了?
You should have kept it till the right girl comes along.
你应该留下来直到你的白雪公主出现
Well, I...
嗯 我...
Couldn't give this ring to just anyone.
我不能把戒指再送给任何人
Oh, right, the, um, the inscription.
哦 是啊 那个 因为那个上面刻的字
How'd you know it was inscribed?
你怎么知道上面写什么?
Well, I-Isn't that the custom?
哦 我...我不知道 这是习俗?
Uh, I just assumed it was.
哦 我只是猜猜罢了
Well, uh, listen, I-I've got to get some fresh rags.
哦 好了 听着  我得去换身衣服了
Uh, thanks for the check. I'll see you around.
哦 谢谢你的支票 回见
Oh, you can count on it.
噢 这点你放心好了
Are you sure? Yes.
- 你确定吗? - 是的
I peed on five different sticks.
我用五根验孕棒测过了
Would you put that burrito away? It's making me nauseous.
你能把那玉米饼拿远点吗? 那让我觉得恶心
Join the club. Look, I-I know
你要习惯 听着..我 我知道
Your parents are religious, but I know this clinic.
你的父母都信教 但我知道有一家诊所
Absotely not!
绝对不行!
So what other choice do we have?
那我们还有什么别的选择?
Well, gee, you could, like, uh, marry me?
哦 天 你可以 比如说 哦 娶我?
Marry you?! I can't stand you.
娶你?! 我受不了你
Oh, nice way to talk to the mother of your child!
哦  你就这样和你孩子的妈妈说话吗!
Oh, god.
哦 天哪
Bathroom.
洗手间
Hey.
嗨
Julie.
Julie
Hi. Uh, hey.
嗨 哦 嗨
Your door was open. Can I come in?
你的门是开的 我能进来吗?
Uh, wh-what are you doing here?
哦 你来这干嘛?
I read your letter.
我读了你的信
I had no idea it would be so sweet.
我不知道你会写得那么感人
I could really tell it came from your heart.
我看的出那是出自你的真心
I'm embarrassed to admit, I...
不怕你笑话 我...
Cried.
我哭了
Uh, my aunt Edie sor of tied one on last night.
哦 我阿姨Edie昨天晚上喝醉了
Oh.
哦
Anyway, I-I guess what I'm saying is...
不管怎么样 我...我想我要说的是...
Okay.
行
"Okay"? Uh...
"行"? 哦...
We can try again.
我们可以再试一下
Julie, that's great! And I want to talk about this,
Julie 太好了! 我想和你好好谈谈
Uh, but I just kinda need to take care of my aunt.
但我现在得去照顾我阿姨
Can I call you tomorrow?
我明天给你电话行吗?
Sure. Oh, we're gonna have to take things slow,
当然 哦 我们得慢慢来
'Cause it'll be a while before I can trust you again.
在我再次相信你之前需要一些时间
I understand.
我明白
Thank you, Bruno. The veal was excellent.
谢谢 Bruno 牛肉很不错
Feel like dessert? No, thank you. I'm stuffed.
- 要不要甜点? - 不用了 谢谢 我吃饱了
Then let me propose a toast.
让我们举杯
To a delightful evening,
为这个令人愉快的夜晚
And to the happy accident that brought us together.
为那场小小的意外让我们相识
Victor, you are so full of crap.
VIictor 你不要再装了
What?
什么?
There was no accident.
那根本不是什么意外
I know you told your chauffeur to ram my car. Why would I do that?
- 我知道是你让你司机来撞我的车 - 为什么我要那样做?
Uh, for the same reason you forgot to sign the check.
哦 和你忘了支票签名是同一样原因
You've been working me since the second we met,
从我们第二次见面开始 你就在打我主意
And I've been on to you every step of the way.
你想要干什么我都了如指掌
What? What's so funny?
怎么? 有什么好笑的?
I just called you a manipulative jerk.
我刚刚叫你操纵狂
I think I underestimated you.
我想我低估了你
I also think this relationship just got a lot more interesting.
我也在想我们的恋爱关系会更加有趣
There is no relationship. This is our last date.
我是不会和你谈恋爱的 这是我们最后一次约会
You didn't have any fun?
你不开心吗?
It was okay. You know, you told a few good jokes.
很好 你知道 你说了几个很好笑的笑话
You're sorta charming.
你还算有魅力
You're not bad-looking. I just think I can do better.
你长得也不错 但我想我能找到比你要好的
Have you not noticed? I'm a catch.
你没注意到吗? 我可是钻石王老五
I have noticed, and I'm throwing you back.
我注意到了 但是我不接受
Gaby, let me tell you something.
Gaby 让我告诉你
For my whole life,
在我整个一生当中
Whenever I've truly wanted something,
如果我真的想要得到什么
I've always gotten it.
我都能得到的
And tonight, right around the time
You were calling me a manipulative jerk,
今天晚上就在你叫我"操纵狂"的时候
I decided I truly want... you.
我更坚定了想... 要你
So brace yourself.
做好准备吧
The chase is on.
追求已经开始了
You can chase me all you want,
你想追当然可以追
But trust me, I'm way too fast for you.
但是相信我 你是追不到我的
Bruno...
Bruno
I'm gonna marry that girl.
我要和那个女人结婚
Can I just say something?
我能说几句吗
You are way hotter than your online profile.
你本人比网上的照片辣多了
So many guys say that.
不少人都这么说
Mmm.
What's wrong?
怎么啦
Oh, my friend's kid is out there.
我朋友的孩子在外面
Oh. Hey, I got an idea.
嘿 我有个主意
Let's go upstairs.
我们上楼吧
I should warn you--
我得警告你
My therapist says I'm sexually compulsive.
我的医师说我有点性强迫
This could take hours.
得要好几小时
Whatever your issues are,
无论你有什么问题
We will work them out together.
我们都会一同解决
(Moans)
It's almost 11:00.
差不多11点了
What is he doing out there by himself?
他自己在外面做什么呢
I'm sure his folks know he's out there.
我保证他的家人知道他在那儿
Now relax.
放松
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
I will be right back. I promise.
我保证 很快就回来
Hey, Travers, what are you doing out here?
Tracers 你在这做什么呢
Where's your mom?
你妈妈呢
She had to go visit a sick friend.
她得去看望一个生病的朋友
Come on.
过来
No way. I didn't come over here to babysit some little brat.
没门 我来这儿不是来照顾一个小鬼的
Shh. He can hear you.
他听得见的
I don't care.
我不在乎
Look, his mother's bound to be home soon, all right?
他妈妈很快就回来了 真的
Then we can pick up where we left off.
那时我们再继续
Forget it.
忘了吧
I'm officially no longer in the mood.
我没那心情了
Sorry I ruined your date.
抱歉我毁了你的约会
That's okay.
没事
She was a very bad lady
她是一个非常坏的女士
Who wanted to do very, very bad things to me.
她想对我做很坏很坏的事
Night, Raoul.
晚安 Raoul
你儿子在我那--Carlos
Where the hell have you been?
你到底去哪了?
Oh, I, uh...
我
Ducked out... just for an hour.
偷跑出去了 就一小时
That's funny, 'cause I found Travers
Wandering the streets three hours ago.
真好笑 因为我发现Travers 三个小时前就在街上游荡
Look, he was fine when I left.
我走时他蛮好的
I just didn't know he'd go outside.
我只是不知道他出去了
Yeah, you never know what an 8 year old's gonna do.
你永远不知道一个八岁小孩会做什么
That's why you supervise him.
所以你得看着他
Hey, you don't get to judge me. You don't have a kid.
你没资格评价我 你又没孩子
Well, if I did,
如果我有的话
I'd treat him a hell of a lot better than you do.
比起你来 我会待他好得多
Ank god he lives with his father. I mean, come on.
感谢上帝他和爸爸一起住 我是说 瞧瞧你自己
What kind of mother are you?
你这算什么母亲
If you are done lecturing me,
如果你教训完我了
I would like my son now.
我现在想要我的儿子
He's asleep.
他睡着了
Come and get him in the morning...
明早过来接他
When you're sober.
你清醒的时候
Hey, buddy!
嘿 伙计
Ur mom's here for ya.
妈妈来接你了
I know you think I'm a terrible person.
我知道你觉得我是个糟糕的人
I never said that.
我从未这么说过
Terrible mother, terrible person--
糟糕的妈妈 糟糕的人
It's the same thing.
这是一回事
Because no matter what else she does,
因为不管她 其他方面如何
If a woman isn't a good mother, she's a failure, right?
如果一个女人不是个好妈妈 她就是个失败的人 不是吗
Look, um...
那个
When I had Travers, I, uh, I knew I was in over my head,
当我怀Travers时 我就很清楚自己这一点
And when charles and I split, I...
所以当我和Charles分开后
I gave him custody.
我给了他看护权
Because I wanted my son to have the best life possible.
因为我想要我的儿子尽可能的过上 最好的生活
And that doesn't make me a good mother, but...
我这样做不是个好母亲 但是
I like to think it makes me a realistic one.
我喜欢这样想这么做是最现实的
Hey, mom.
妈妈
Hey, champ.
小调皮
I missed you.
我想你
Oh, I missed you, too.
我也想你
Guess what?
知道吗
I've got so many fun things for you to do today.
今天我为你准备了很多好玩的事情
Cool. Yeah.
- 真好 - 好
Thanks for the ice cream.
谢谢你的冰淇淋
My pleasure. I'll see you, little man.
很高兴你喜欢 待会见 小男子汉
Hey.
Travers said he's, uh, staying at least a month.
Travers说至少会待一个月
Yeah.
So if you ever need a babysitter, just yell.
如果你需要保姆 就说
I appreciate that.
谢谢
Hey! Wait for me!
等等我
No, I don't want a viola player.
不 我不需要中提琴手
I asked for a violinist. I don't even know what a viola is.
我要的是小提琴手 我甚至都不知道 中提琴是用来干嘛的
Oh, it's just a big violin?
就是个大的小提琴?
Okay. Yeah, sure.
好吧 当然
Okay, I'll see you at 8:00. (Telhone beeps)
八点见
What was that?
那是什么
It's... just a little surprise, okay?
就是一点小惊喜 好吗
Let it go.
别问了
"Let it go"-- That's cute.
"别问了" 很有意思啊
Start talkin'.
开始说
I planned a little something for our anniversary.
我为我们的周年纪念计划了一点小东西
That is all I'm gonna say.
那就是我要说的
Okay. Okay. Okay. If we're doing this,
好吧好吧 如果我们要做的话
I need to buy you something.
我得给你买点什么
What do you want?
你想要什么
You don't have to buy me anything.
你不需要给我买任何东西
Well, you didn't have to plan anything,
你不需要计划什么的
But you did, even though we had an agreement.
但是你做了 我们得一致才行
You like ties? You're getting a tie.
你喜欢领带吗 你会得到一条的
What are you getting ???
你怎么这么烦呢?
I have been dragging my ass all day, and the only thought
我跑了一整天了 唯一支撑我
That's kept me going is the hot bath,
继续下去的就是一个热水澡
And now I have do my hair and shave my legs.
我得洗洗头发 刮刮腿毛
So what do you want to do, Lynette?
你想做什么呢 Lynette
Just tell me what you want.
告诉我你想要什么就行
I told you what I want.
我告诉你我想要的
Hot bath, bed early, but you che not to listen.
一个热水澡 早早上床 但是你不听
Well, okay, I guess I can just cancel the whole thing.
好吧 我想我可以取消这一切
You can have your dream evening alone,
你可以一人去享受梦幻一夜
And I'll get up a poker game or something.
我会玩点扑克或别的
Thank you.
谢谢
Hey.you know what? I've been dragging my ass all day, too,
你知道吗 我也忙了一天了
And you know what got me through it?
你知道是什么支撑着我吗?
The idea of doing something special with you.
就是想和你一起做点特别的事
Happy anniversary.
周年快乐
All right. I'm off to join your mother.
好了 我出发去找你们妈妈
The hotel number's on the fridge in case there's a problem.
要是有什么事的话 旅馆号码就在冰箱上
Bree said her cell phone isn't getting good reception.
Bree说她的手机信号不好
Uh, actually, we--we kinda already have a problem.
事实上 我们已经有点小问题了
Well, I'm already late for my flight.
我要误航班了
Can this wait a few weeks till we're back?
能等我们几周后回来再说吗
Yeah, this could wait a few weeks. Oh, good.
- 是的 能等几个星期 - 好的
I mean, heck, this particular problem could wait...
我是说 这个特别的问题能够等
Nine months.
9个月
Good lord.
老天
How was your bath?
你洗得如何
Oh, I couldn't relax.
我都不能放松下来
I just kept replaying the fight I had with Tom in my head.
我脑子里一直想着我跟Tom吵架的事
Well, at least your husband tries to be romantic.
至少你丈夫试着来点浪漫的
Every anniversary, Gilbert bought me an appliance.
每次周年纪念 Gilbert都会给我买生活用品
The last one, he gave me a vacuum cleaner.
最后一次 他送了我台吸尘器
He died two weeks later.
两个星期后他就死了
I didn't cry.
我没有哭
Wow.
哇喔
Who could that be? Here.
会是谁呢 给
All right. Here's what we're thinking.
好吧 这就是我们想的
Clearly, the idea
Of the two of you getting married is ridiculous.
很明显 你俩结婚的这个主意很荒谬
So what do you want me to do?
你想要我做什么呢
Glad you asked.
很高兴你问到了
Bree and I have decided
Bree和我已经决定了
That Danielle will join us on our heymoon.
Danielle将和我们一起去度蜜月
When we return, we'll tell our friends
当我们回来后 我会告诉我们的朋友们
She's decided to study abroad. Once the baby is born
她决定出国学习 孩子生下来后
And adopted by a suitable family,
再找个合适的家庭收养他
She'll come home.
她就会回家的
What about me?
那我怎么办
You leave.
你将离开
Leave?
离开?
Get out of fairview and don't tell a soul why,
什么也别说 从大家视野中消失
Not even your aunt. I can't do that.
- 甚至是你的阿姨 - 我做不到
Why not? Because I've got responsibilities here.
- 为什么? - 因为我在这里还有责任
People are counting on me. Yeah, well, you should have thought of that
Before you impregnated my stepdaughter.
- 有人需要我 - 是啊 你该在让我继女怀孕之前想到这一点的
I said I'm not leaving! Oh,easy there, turbo.
- 我说了我不走! - 噢 别激动 这么大火气
Uh... we'll be right back.
我们一会就回来
So who exactly is counting on you?
到底是谁需要你?
Hmm? Julie Mayer, maybe?
恩? 或许是Julie Mayer?
She gave me another chance.
她给了我另一次机会
I can't leave if I've still got a shot with her.
如果我跟她还有可能 我就不能走
And what's gonna happen
但是如果Julie发现
When Julie finds out you knocked up my sister? Didn't your stepdad just say
我妹妹怀了你的孩子- Julie会怎么想? - 你后爹不是刚说过
No one's gonna find out about that?
不会有人发现这件事吗
Okay.
好吧
Try this.
这么说吧
Julie's a nice girl,
Julie是个好女孩
And you, well...
而你...
You're a dog.
你是个不安分的人
No knock.
不是打击你
I'm a dog lover myself,
我就喜欢这样的人
But Julie deserves better.
但Julie值得更好的人
You know you'll just end up cheating on her.
你知道你最后还是会背着她乱搞的
No, I won't hurt her again.
不 我不会再伤害她的
Sure you will.
你肯定会的
Not right away.
现在不会而已
Maybe you'll hold out for six months,
或许你会坚持半年吧
But then it'll hurt her even more.
但是那样 会伤她更深的
Am I wrong?
我说错了吗?
You just have to ask yourself
问问你自己吧
If you can be the kind of guy she needs you to be.
你是不是她想要找的那个人
If you can't...
如果你不是....
Walk away.
那就走开吧
Beer is on the house, guys.
啤酒来了 伙计们
Drink fast, get stupid, lose money.
大口喝 灌倒自己 多多输钱
Mike!
Hey.
嘿
(Tom) how's it going, buddy?
你好吗 伙计
Hey, you know, uh, Orson, right?
嘿 你认识Orson 对吧
Oh, yeah.
噢 是的
Hey, neighbor.
嘿 邻居
Hey, so let's get started, huh?
嘿 我们开始吧 好吗
5-Card stud? $2 ante?
5张梭哈? 每次下注两块?
Good evening, gentlemen.
晚上好 先生们
Ian!
Ian
Hey... Ian.
嘿 Ian
Nice to see you, Mike.
很高兴见到你 Mike
(Lowered voice) what is fish and chips doing here?
这英国快餐跑这儿来干吗?
(Lowered voice) Susan asked me to include him.
Susan让我叫他的
Said he always wanted to learn how to play poker.
说他一直想学怎么打牌
So we're going to give him some very expensive lessons.
所以我们得给他"宝贵"的一课
Be careful. He already knows how to bluff.
小心点 他已经学会怎么"耍诈"了
Hey.
嘿
Hey. How's it going?
嘿 你好吗?
Good. Good, uh...
很好 很好
Just wanted to tell you, I have to leave town for a while.
我是来告诉你 我要离开这里一段时间
Really? Is something wrong?
真的吗? 出了什么事吗
No, no, no. It's just family stuff.
不 不 不是的 只是家里的事
I don't know exactly when I'll be back.
我也不知道具体什么时候回来
It could be a while, though.
可能会有段时间
Oh.
噢
Okay.
好吧
I just want you know that...
我只是想你明白
It means a lot that you were willing to give me a second chance.
你再给我一次机会 对我来说意义重大
You're, like, the only person that's ever done that.
你是唯一一个这么做的人
Austin... what's going on?
Austin 到底是怎么了
Nothing, uh, it's just...
没什么...只是...
I have to go.
我该走了
Good-bye, Julie.
再见 Julie
Austin!
I'll raise you.
我再加钱
Mm. Out.
不跟
Ah, another courageous move for "foldilocks."
不是人人都有勇气啊
All right. I'll call you.
好了 我跟
Flush, king high.
同花顺 最大是K
Full house, 7s and knaves.
三带二 三张7 一对儿Knave
Jacks. We call them jacks.
J 我们叫J
Boy, this is your lucky room.
小伙子 这是你的幸运房间啊
Yes, I heard about your engagement the other night.
是啊 我听说那晚你在这里求婚的
Congratulations.
恭喜啊
Yeah, about that, Ian,
是啊 说到那件事 Ian
Was that, uh, proposal spontaneous,
求婚是突然想到的
Or did you have it all planned?
还是你都计划好的
Oh, it was entirely planned.
噢 是都计划好的
I thought it would be the ideal occasion.
我觉得当时是很理想的环境
Wow. Well, if it was planned, why didn't you have a ring?
喔 那你怎么会连戒指都没准备呢
Well, I thought Susan might like to choose the ring herself.
我想Susan或许愿意自己去挑戒指
Ante up, boys.
下注啊 伙计们
So why'd she pick a ring that was too big for her?
那她干吗选一枚自己戴起来大的戒指呢?
How did you know that?
你怎么知道的
Guys, guys, guys, guys, we came here to play cards.
伙计们 伙计们 伙计们 伙计们 我们是来打牌的
Why are we talking about jewelry?
谈什么珠宝首饰啊
Sorry, Tom, but I just found out
抱歉Tom 但我只是发现
I bought a ring for Susan myself.
我自己也给Susan买了一枚戒指
It was in my pocket that night
那晚就放在我的口袋里
So son of a bitch ran me over.
结果被个杂种把我给撞了
Hey, Tom's right. We should focus on the game.
嘿 Tom说的对 我们专心打牌吧
After our talk, I called the hospital.
我们谈过之后 我打电话给医院
They said my ring got in with your wife's stuff.
他们说我的戒指被放到你妻子的东西里了
So you saw it before I did...
所以你在我之前看到了...
The same day you proposed to Susan.
就在那天你向Susan求婚了
And your point is?
你想说的是?
That that's why you were in such a big hurry.
这就是为什么你这么着急
You wanted to seal the deal
你想赶紧搞定一切
Before I found out about the ring and told her.
在我发现戒指 并告诉她之前
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
你是以为我怕你吗
Maybe you should be.
或许你是应该
What do you think Susan would say
你觉得Susan会说什么?
If she found out why your proposal was so spontaneous?
如果她发现你的求婚是这么的突然
Guys, can we just play?
伙计们 打牌好吗?
I'm trying.
我尽量
Fine.
好吧
Deal.
该你了
Hello?
喂?
Mr. Scavo,
Scavo先生
It's Lamar from the Limo service.
我是Limo服务公司的Lamar
Uh, I got a flat,
我的车子坏了
So I might be late picking up you and your wife.
所以我可能会晚点去接你和你太太
What are you talking about? I-I-I canceled you.
你在说什么啊? 我...我不是跟你取消了吗
No, you didn't. Yes, I did. I left you a message.
- 不 你没有 - 我有的 我有留言给你啊
Oh, I must have missed it.
噢 我一定是没收到
Anyway, I dropped your wife off, right where you told me.
总之呢 我把你妻子放在你告诉我的地方了
Oh, god. When?
噢 上帝啊 什么时候的事?
About two hours ago.
大概两小时前
Guys, um, lock up when you're done.
伙计们 你们完事儿锁好门
I'll open.
我先来
I'm out.
不跟
And I'll raise you.
我加钱
You want a beer?
你要啤酒吗
Hell, Tom's gone. Let's go open up the good stuff.
该死 Tome走了 我们自己去找点好东西吧
Well...
恩...
Looks like it's just you and me,
看来就剩下咱俩了
If you're still in.
如果你还继续的话
With this hand? You bet I am.
这一手牌? 当然了
I'll re-raise.
我再加
And raise again.
再加
Your stack's looking kinda small.
你的筹码看起来少了点
Will you taka check?
你收支票吗
You know I can't match that.
你知道我没钱继续跟
How about this, then?
那这样好不好
You win, you keep the money,
你赢了 钱都归你
And you tell Susan whatever you want.
你还可以把你想说的都告诉Susan
I win, you keep your mouth shut about the ring,
我赢了 你就再也不许提戒指的事
And you leave me and Susan alone.
并且离我和Susan远远的
Deal.
成交
How was the game?
牌打得怎样
I won.
我赢了
Lynette, I am so sorry. I am so sorry!
Lynette 我很抱歉 对不起
You see, there was supposed to be a horse-drawn carriage and--
瞧 这本该是有一辆马车的...
Oh, good. You got the flowers.
噢 很好 你收到花了
Coffee?
咖啡?
Yes, please.
是的 谢谢
Yeah, she-- She likes coffee, too. Thanks.
是的 她...她也要咖啡 谢谢
I'm really, really,really sorry...
我真的真的很...
Please stop apologizing.
不要再道歉了
I'm s-- I appreciate what you were trying to do.
- 我... - 我很感激你原本想要做的
It was a lovely though
很美好的想法
That just went hideously, hideously, hideously wrong.
只是结果变的非常非常非常糟糕
Wait till the kids find out that you saw a real coyote.
孩子要是知道你见过活的郊狼的话....
Hideously.
还是糟糕
Well, I learned my lesson.
好吧 我得到教训了
Never again. No more surprises.
再也不要想制造惊喜
From now on, I'll do exactly what you say.
从现在开始 我就完全按照你说的去做
Oh, don't. You... dare.
噢 你...你敢
What?
什么?
I had a lot of time to think tonight,
我想了很久今晚的事
And I realized you were right.
我想你是对的
We have to keep the romance going,
我们要保持浪漫
No matter how tired we are.
不管我们有多累
The only thing worse thaor just going through the motions
比光想不做更糟糕的是
Is not bothering to go through the motions.
连想都不肯想
So you want me to surprise you next year?
那么 你希望我明年也给你准备惊喜?
Knock yourself out.
让你自己吃惊吧
Just wait, 'cause I will think of something even better.
你就等着吧 因为我会构思出更好的主意
Well, after this year,
有了今年这回
I would be happy with any date
任何约会都够让我开心的了
That included food and shelter.
只要有吃有住就行
Nine years.
9年纪念快乐
Nine years...
9年快乐
And I have loved every minute of it.
每一份钟我都没有停止过爱你
Me, too.
我也是
(Rex) take a drive down any street in suburbia.
在郊区的任何一条街上开车
Know what you're gonna see?
知道你会看到什么吗?
A bunch of guys wearing the same expression.
有着同样表情的一群男人们
It's a look that says,
那表情在说
"Oh, crap.
"噢 该死"
My dreams are never gonna come true."
"我的梦想永远不会实现了"
"I'll never have a life free from scandal."
"我永远无法摆脱这种荒谬的生活了"
"I'll never have a son of my own."
"我永远不会有自己的儿子了"
"I'll never hold her in my arms again."
"我再也无法拥她入怀了"
"I'll never get to tell her how I feel."
我永远也没有机会告诉她我的感受了
Yeah, the suburbs are filled with a lot of men who have given up hope.
的确 在郊区的男人有很多都放弃了希望
Of course, every once in a while you do come across some lucky S.O.B.
当然偶尔 你会碰到那种走运的家伙
whose dreams have all come true.
他的梦想可以成真
You know how you spot them?
你知道怎样能认出他们吗?
They're the ones who can't stop smiling.
那些脸上止不住笑容的人
Don't you just hate those guys?
这种人是不是让你觉得很可恨?